Guide to the Anne Morrow Lindbergh Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Family correspondence and personal files, 1906-1974; Series II
  - Family correspondence
    - Cutter, Annie Spencer, 1914-1957, undated (Box 25, Folder 7-14)
    - Feydy, Anne (Lindbergh)
      See: Lindbergh, Anne Spencer, boxes 47-49, folders 337-370
    - Feydy, Charles, 1969-1973 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Feydy, Hélène, 1960-1973 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Feydy, Jacqueline, 1963-1973 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Fulenwider, Constance (Morrow), 1949-1973 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Greathouse, Rebekah (Scandrett), 1934-1955 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Hutchins, Saran (Morgan), 1950-1973, undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Kenney, Susan (McIlvaine), 1964-1966 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Kenney, Susan (McIlvaine), 1967-1972, undated (Box 26, Folder 22-24)
    - Land, Elizabeth (Stiles), 1933-1944, undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Land, Emory Scott, 1931-1969 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Leighton, Blair, 1965-1967 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Leighton, J. Kenric, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Leighton, Katherine (McIlvaine), 1917-1971, undated (Box 26, Folder 29-30)
    - Lindbergh, Alika, 1969-1972 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1911-1924 (Box 26, Folder 32-41)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1925-1928 October 22 (Box 27, Folder 42-56)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1928 October 23-1931 August (Box 28, Folder 57-70)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1931 September-1933 September (Box 29, Folder 71-83)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1933 October-1935 (Box 30, Folder 84-95)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1936 January-1936 October 26 (Box 31, Folder 96-107)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1936 October 27-1937 July 15 (Box 32, Folder 108-121)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1937 July 16-1938 September (Box 33, Folder 122-135)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1938 October-1939 (Box 34, Folder 136-149)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1940-1942 July (Box 35, Folder 150-164)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1942 August-1944 July (Box 36, Folder 165-183)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1944 August-1946 July (Box 37, Folder 184-198)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1946 August-1947 October (Box 38, Folder 199-214)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1947 November-1950 July 10 (Box 39, Folder 215-232)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1950 July 11-1953 (Box 40, Folder 233-249)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1954-1959 March (Box 41, Folder 250-264)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1959 April-1962 June (Box 42, Folder 265-277)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1962 July-1965 April (Box 43, Folder 278-292)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1965 May-1968 August (Box 44, Folder 293-307)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1968 September-1971 November (Box 45, Folder 308-321)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1971 December-1973 September (Box 46, Folder 322-334)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1973 October-1974, undated (Box 47, Folder 335-336)
    - Lindbergh, Anne Spencer, 1944-1954 (Box 47, Folder 337-339)
    - Lindbergh, Anne Spencer, 1955-1966 (Box 48, Folder 340-354)
    - Lindbergh, Anne Spencer, 1967-1973, undated (Box 49, Folder 355-370)
    - Lindbergh, Barbara (Robbins), 1953-1974 (Box 50, Folder 371-377)
    - Lindbergh, Charles Augustus, 1928-1950 July (Box 50, Folder 378-386)
    - Lindbergh, Charles Augustus, 1950 August-1974, undated (Box 51, Folder 387-401)
    - Lindbergh, Erin Elisabeth, 1968-1973 (Box 51, Folder 402)
    - Lindbergh, Evangeline Lodge (Land), 1928-1932 March (Box 51, Folder 403-404)
    - Lindbergh, Evangeline Lodge (Land), 1932 April-1948, undated (Box 52, Folder 405-416)
    - Lindbergh, Jon Morrow, 1937-1953 (Box 52, Folder 417-422)
    - Lindbergh, Jon Morrow, 1954-1972, undated (Box 53, Folder 423-425)
    - Lindbergh, Kristine, 1959-1972 (Box 53, Folder 426)
    - Lindbergh, Land Morrow, 1940-1967 (Box 53, Folder 427-433)
    - Lindbergh, Leif, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 434)
    - Lindbergh, Peter Morrow, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 435)
    - Lindbergh, Reeve Morrow, 1950-1961 (Box 53, Folder 436-439)
    - Lindbergh, Reeve Morrow, 1962-1974, undated (Box 54, Folder 440-448)
    - Lindbergh, Scott Morrow, 1947-1967 (Box 54, Folder 449-456)
    - Lindbergh, Scott Morrow, 1968-1973, undated (Box 55, Folder 457)
    - Lindbergh, Susan (Miller), 1959-1973 (Box 55, Folder 458-461)
    - Lindbergh, Wendy, 1960-1973 (Box 55, Folder 462)
    - Loines, Katharine, 1942-1955 (Box 55, Folder 463)
    - McIlvaine, Edwin Linton, 1935-1939 (Box 55, Folder 464)
    - McIlvaine, Hilda (Morrow), 1930-1941 (Box 55, Folder 465)
    - McIlvaine, James Morrow, 1922-1938 (Box 55, Folder 466)
    - McIlvaine, Katherine
      See: Leighton, Katherine (McIlvaine), box 26, folders 29-30
    - McIlvaine, Ruth
      See: Voorhees, Ruth (McIlvaine), box 66, folder 672
    - McIlvaine, Susan
      See: Kenney, Susan (McIlvaine), boxes 25-26, folders 21-24
    - McIlvaine, Virginia, 1955-1972 (Box 55, Folder 467)
    - Miller, Helen, 1955-1963 (Box 55, Folder 468)
    - Miller, James W., 1959-1966 (Box 55, Folder 469)
    - Miller, Mary, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 470)
    - Miller, Pamela (Siln), 1972 (Box 55, Folder 471)
    - Miller, Peter, 1954-1960 (Box 55, Folder 472)
    - Miller, Susan, 1954-1960
      See: Lindbergh, Susan (Miller), box 55, folders 458-461
    - Miller, Tom, 1956-1972 (Box 55, Folder 473)
    - Miller, William W., 1954-1962 (Box 55, Folder 474)
    - Morgan, Aubrey Niel, 1934-1939, 1972-1973 (Box 55, Folder 475)
    - Morgan, Constance (Morrow), 1923-1930 (Box 55, Folder 476-482)
    - Morgan, Constance (Morrow), 1931-1951 (Box 56, Folder 483-501)
    - Morgan, Constance (Morrow), 1952-1960 (Box 57, Folder 502-519)
    - Morgan, Constance (Morrow), 1961-1971 (Box 58, Folder 520-535)
    - Morgan, Constance (Morrow), 1972-1973, undated (Box 59, Folder 536-540)
    - Morgan, Edith, 1934-1955 (Box 59, Folder 541)
    - Morgan, Elisabeth Angharad
      See: Pendleton, Elisabeth (Morgan), box 65, folder 646
    - Morgan, Elisabeth (Morrow)
      See: Morrow, Elisabeth Reeve, box 63, folders 617-621
    - Morgan, Janet, 1936 (Box 59, Folder 542)
    - Morgan, Margaret, 1935-1949 (Box 59, Folder 543-544)
    - Morgan, Margaret Constance Eiluned, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 545)
    - Morgan, Rhidian Morrow Morgan, 1956-1973 (Box 59, Folder 546)
    - Morgan, Richard, 1960 (Box 59, Folder 547)
    - Morgan, Saran Niel
      See: Hutchins, Saran (Morgan), box 25, folder 20
    - Morrow, A. Herman, 1921 (Box 59, Folder 548)
    - Morrow, Alice, 1938 (Box 59, Folder 549)
    - Morrow, Anne Spencer
      See: Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), boxes 26-47, folders 32-336
    - Morrow, Constance Cutter
      See: Morgan, Constance (Morrow), boxes 55-59, folders 476-540
    - Morrow, Dwight Whitney, Sr., 1920-1925 (Box 59, Folder 550)
    - Morrow, Dwight Whitney, Jr., 1925-1963 August (Box 59, Folder 551-559)
    - Morrow, Dwight Whitney, Jr., 1963 September-1973, undated (Box 60, Folder 560-568)
    - Morrow, Elizabeth (Cutter), 1906-1933 August (Box 60, Folder 569-577)
    - Morrow, Elizabeth (Cutter), 1933 September-1939 (Box 61, Folder 578-594)
    - Morrow, Elizabeth (Cutter), 1940-1949 (Box 62, Folder 595-608)
    - Morrow, Elizabeth (Cutter), 1950-1954, undated (Box 63, Folder 609-616)
    - Morrow, Elisabeth Reeve, 1915-1934, undated (Box 63, Folder 617-621)
    - Morrow, Faith
      See: Williams, Faith (Morrow), box 66, folder 674
    - Morrow, Hattie, 1924-1933 (Box 63, Folder 622)
    - Morrow, Jay Johnson, 1923-1937 (Box 63, Folder 623-625)
    - Morrow, Margot (Loines), 1935-1940 (Box 63, Folder 626-628)
    - Morrow, Margot (Loines), 1941-1972 (Box 64, Folder 629-642)
    - Morrow, Margot (Loines), 1973, undated (Box 65, Folder 643)
    - Morrow, Nancy Lofton, 1970-1974 (Box 65, Folder 644)
    - Morrow, Stephen Dwight, 1959-1970 (Box 65, Folder 645)
    - Pendleton, Elisabeth (Morgan), 1954-1973, undated (Box 65, Folder 646)
    - Pendleton, Miles Stevens, Jr., 1958 (Box 65, Folder 647)
    - Robbins, Barbara Helen
      See: Lindbergh, Barbara (Robbins), box 50, folders 371-377
    - Robbins, Bonnie, 1965-1972 (Box 65, Folder 648)
    - Robbins, Jane O., 1953-1964 (Box 65, Folder 649)
    - Robbins, James, 1955-1956 (Box 65, Folder 650)
    - Robbins, Richard J., 1957 (Box 65, Folder 651)
    - Robbins, Ruth, 1954-1963 (Box 65, Folder 652)
    - Robbins, Sophie, 1953-1968 (Box 65, Folder 653)
    - Robbins, Wendy
      See: Vogel, Wendy (Robbins), box 66, folder 671
    - Scandrett, Agnes (Morrow), 1926-1948, undated (Box 65, Folder 654-655)
    - Scandrett, Jay Johnson Morrow, 1917-1926 October (Box 65, Folder 656-663)
    - Scandrett, Jay Johnson Morrow, 1926 November-1958 (Box 66, Folder 664-667)
    - Scandrett, Mary (Landenberger), 1930-1967, undated (Box 66, Folder 668)
    - Scandrett, Richard B., Jr., 1914-1955, undated (Box 66, Folder 669-670)
    - Vogel, Wendy (Robbins), 1957-1972 (Box 66, Folder 671)
    - Voorhees, Ruth (McIlvaine), 1927-1962, undated (Box 66, Folder 672)
    - Wilkie, John, 1957 (Box 66, Folder 673)
    - Wilkie, Margot (Loines)
      See: Morrow, Margot (Loines), boxes 63-65, folders 626-643
    - Williams, Faith (Morrow), 1959-1973 (Box 66, Folder 674)
    - Yates, Cynthia (Knoch), 1955-1963 (Box 66, Folder 675)
    - Yates, David Spencer, 1962-1972 (Box 66, Folder 676)
    - Yates, Edith (Cutter), 1918-1972, undated (Box 66, Folder 677-679)
    - Yates, Robert S., 1972 (Box 66, Folder 680)
  - Personal files
    - Cutter, Annie Spencer
      - Financial and legal papers, 1955-1957 (Box 67, Folder 681)
      - Memorial service arrangements, 1957 (Box 67, Folder 682)
      - Condolences on her death, 1957 (Box 67, Folder 683)
    - Fulenwider, Constance (Morrow), 1957 (Box 67, Folder 684)
      Commencement program, newspaper clippings
    - Hutchins, Saran (Morgan), 1963 (Box 67, Folder 685)
      Newspaper clippings
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1929 (Box 67, Folder 686)
      Bridal register
    - Lindbergh, Anne Spencer, 1940
      - Correspondence, cards on her birth, 1940 (Box 67, Folder 687)
      - Wedding, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 688)
    - Lindbergh, Charles Augustus, Jr.
      Weight chart
      - Weight chart, 1930, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 689)
      - Correspondence re: birth to Anne Morrow and Charles Augustus Lindbergh, 1930 May-June (Box 67A, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence re: birth to Elizabeth C. Morrow and Dwight W. Morrow, 1930 June-July (Box 67A, Folder 2)
      - Memories of Charles Augustus Lindbergh, Jr.
        - Diary of Betty Gow (copy) and letter to Elizabeth C. Morrow, Circa 1932 August (Box 67A, Folder 3)
        - Notes by Elizabeth C. Morrow, [Circa 1932] (Box 67A, Folder 4)
        - Reminiscence of Aida Breckinridge and speech by Henry Breckinridge, 1932 February 27, undated (Box 67A, Folder 5)
      - Hair clippings, envelope that held, 1932 (Box 67A, Folder 6)
      - Hair clippings, 1932 (Box 67B)
        Conditions Governing Access
        Materials in in box 67B may only be used under the supervision of Public Services staff.
      - Newsclippings and kidnapping information poster, 1930, 1932 (Box 67A, Folder 7)
      - Photo lists and orders, Circa 1932, undated (Box 67A, Folder 8)
    - Lindbergh, Jon Morrow
      - Correspondence on his birth, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 690)
      - Cards, notes on his birth, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 691)
      - Telegrams on his birth, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 692-693)
    - Lindbergh, Land Morrow, 1937 (Box 67, Folder 694)
      Correspondence, telegrams on his birth
    - Lindbergh, Reeve Morrow
      - Correspondence on her birth, 1945 (Box 68, Folder 695)
      - Cards, telegrams on her birth, 1945 (Box 68, Folder 696)
      - Wedding, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 697)
    - Lindbergh, Scott Morrow
      - Correspondence, cards on his birth, 1942 (Box 68, Folder 698)
      - Telegrams on his birth, 1942 (Box 68, Folder 699)
    - Morgan, Constance (Morrow)
      - Writings, Undated (Box 68, Folder 700)
      - Smith College speech, 1955 (Box 68, Folder 701)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 702)
    - Morrow, Dwight Whitney, Sr.
      - The President's Aircraft Board hearings, volumes 1-4, 1925 (Box 68, Folder 703-706)
      - Tributes and condolences on his death (marked "special" by Anne Morrow Lindbergh), 1931 (Box 69, Folder 707-708)
      - Tributes and condolences on his death, 1931 (Box 69, Folder 709-711)
      - Memorial essays and published tributes, 1931-1932 (Box 69, Folder 712)
      - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1930-1936 (Box 69, Folder 713)
      - Reviews of the biography by Harold Nicolson, 1935 (Box 69, Folder 714)
    - Morrow, Dwight Whitney, Jr.
      - Academic syllabus, 1952-1953 (Box 69, Folder 715)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 716)
    - Morrow, Elizabeth (Cutter)
      - Writings, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 717)
        Memorial essay on Charles Augustus, Jr. (1930-1932)
      - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1953-1966 (Box 69, Folder 718)
      - Will, 1952 (Box 69, Folder 719)
      - Memorial service arrangements, 1955 (Box 69, Folder 720)
      - Memorial service arrangements, 1955 (Box 70, Folder 721)
      - Estate
        - Inventory of furniture and household goods at Next Day Hill, New Jersey, 1955 (Box 70, Folder 722)
        - Inventory of personal effects, 1955 (Box 70, Folder 723)
        - Bequests and gifts, 1955-1956 (Box 70, Folder 724)
      - Memorial dedication of Smith College alumnae fund, 1955 (Box 70, Folder 725)
    - Morrow, Elisabeth Reeve
      - Memorial service arrangements, 1934 (Box 71, Folder 726)
      - Condolences on her death, 1934 (Box 71, Folder 727)
    - Morrow, Jay Johnson
      - Transcript of autobiographical letter, 1936 (Box 71, Folder 728)
      - Newspaper clippings and memorial publications on his death, 1937 (Box 71, Folder 729)
    - Sandrett, Jay Johnson Morrow, 1944 (Box 71, Folder 730)
      Writings: "What Goes On"
- Publisher's correspondence, 1930-1973; Series III
  The series is arranged in three sections: Major publishers, Other publishers, and Publishers' announcements. Major publishers is arranged alphabetically by name of company, Other publishers and Publishers' announcements are arranged chronologically.
  Correspondence in the series is incoming and runs from the time of the writing of "Flying Around the North Atlantic" (1934) to Hour of Gold, Hour of Lead (1973). Major publishers represented are Atlantic Monthly; Harcourt, Brace; and Pantheon Books. Other Publishers files include correspondence from Common Sense, Harpers' Bazaar, Readers' Digest, Saturday Review of Literature, and other small publishing firms and magazines.
  Subjects covered in the series include solicitations; routine editing and proofreading issues; book design; contract negotiations; sales and royalties; awards; reprints; and film rights and adaptations. Individuals represented include John Hall Wheelock ( Scribner's ), Dewitt Wallace and Paul Palmer ( Reader's Digest ), Selden Rodman ( Common Sense ), Kyrill Schabert (Pantheon Books), George Stevens ( Saturday Review of Literature ), and William Jovanovich (Harcourt, Brace and World and Harcourt Brace Jovanovich). Their letters contain discussion of general publishing issues as well as comments on Lindbergh's work and critiques of their own work and that of other authors they represent. Lindbergh's substantial correspondence from Helen and Kurt Wolff can be found under Pantheon Books through 1960, and thereafter under Harcourt, Brace and World, and Harcourt Brace Jovanovich. It reveals the intimate, interdependent working relationship between author and editor. In addition to business details and general editing matters, their letters offer encouragement, suggestions for revisions, discussion of general theories of literary production, and comments on Lindbergh's style of creation and development as an author (see Series I Correspondence From Friends and Acquaintances, for the Wolff's personal correspondence with Lindbergh). Charles Lindbergh took an active interest in the publication of Anne's diaries. His correspondence with Helen Wolff and Harcourt Brace Jovanovich can be found in the Charles A. Lindbergh Papers and contains information on contract issues, the gathering and copying of diaries and letters, delivery of manuscripts, and editing revisions.
  - Major publishers
    - Atlantic Monthly, 1939-1966 (Box 72, Folder 1-6)
    - Chatto and Windus
      See: Harcourt, Brace and Company, box 72, folders 7-19
      See: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, box 73, folders 27-30
    - Harcourt, Brace and Company, 1934-1960 (Box 72, Folder 7-19)
    - Harcourt, Brace and World, 1961-1966 (Box 72, Folder 20-22)
    - Harcourt, Brace and World, 1967-1970 (Box 73, Folder 23-26)
    - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, 1971-1973 (Box 73, Folder 27-30)
    - Helen and Kurt Wolff Books
      See: Harcourt, Brace and World, boxes 72-73, folders 20-26
    - Pantheon Books, 1947-1973 (Box 73, Folder 31-40)
    - Random House
      See: Pantheon Books, box 73, folders 31-40
  - Other publishers, 1930-1940 (Box 73, Folder 41-43)
  - Other publishers, 1941-1973, undated (Box 74, Folder 44-61)
  - Publishers' announcements, 1935-1971 (Box 74, Folder 62-63)
- General correspondence, 1916-1974; Series IV
  The series is arranged chronologically.
  The series is comprised of letters that fall into the following categories: personal letters from friends and acquaintances who wrote to Lindbergh fewer than five times; routine business correspondence; autograph requests; letters from the general public commenting on Lindbergh's activities; and requests that Lindbergh give speeches, serve on committees, and write articles on behalf of various religious, cultural, philanthropic, and political causes. Much of the correspondence in the series is routine. Viewed in its entirety, however, it reveals two aspects of Lindbergh's life. First, the close scrutiny to which her life, both public and private, was subjected to an intensely curious public, and second, her great influence and popularity as a writer with its corresponding demands on her time.
  - 1916-1928 (Box 75, Folder 1-13)
  - 1929-1933 June (Box 76, Folder 14-27)
  - 1933 July-1935 December (Box 77, Folder 28-42)
  - 1935, undated-1938 September (Box 78, Folder 43-57)
  - 1938 October-1939 (Box 79, Folder 58-69)
  - 1940 January-December (Box 80, Folder 70-81)
  - 1940, undated-1941 June 16 (Box 81, Folder 82-91)
  - 1941 June 17-1942 March (Box 82, Folder 92-101)
  - 1942 April-1945 June (Box 83, Folder 102-112)
  - 1945 July-1948 June (Box 84, Folder 113-123)
  - 1948 July-1951 March (Box 85, Folder 124-135)
  - 1951 April-1954 September (Box 86, Folder 136-150)
  - 1954 October-1956 (Box 87, Folder 151-165)
  - 1957-1958 (Box 88, Folder 166-179)
  - 1959-1961 (Box 89, Folder 180-192)
  - 1962-1964 March (Box 90, Folder 193-205)
  - 1964 April-1966 (Box 91, Folder 206-219)
  - 1967-1969 September (Box 92, Folder 220-231)
  - 1969 October-1970 (Box 93, Folder 232-242)
  - 1971-1974 January (Box 94, Folder 243-255)
  - Undated (Box 95, Folder 256-261)
- Correspondence from readers, 1934-1973; Series V
  The series is arranged chronologically by publication date of the work to which the letters pertain. For each work, letters are arranged into two groups: General, for persons unknown to Lindbergh, and Personal, for friends and family.
  The series contains letters commenting on Lindbergh's writings. Works that elicited particularly voluminous correspondence are "Prayer for Peace" (1940), "Feeding Europe" (1940), The Wave of the Future (1940), Gift from the Sea (1955), and Bring Me a Unicorn (1971). Letters about "Feeding Europe" also include those that relate to the general question of sending relief to the occupied countries. Letters concerning the Lindberghs' stand on intervention in World War II are included under Wave of the Future.
  The responses of readers to Lindbergh's work frequently center on the themes of mourning and recovery from personal loss; the role of a woman as wife, mother, and creative person; the loneliness and exhilaration of adolescence; and the individual's responsibility to act, whether as a peacemaker, conservationist, or artist. Although Lindbergh described her life as an "extraordinary" one led by "a quite ordinary person," it was her ability to convey the "ordinary," which allowed her readers to identify closely with her. She frequently placed an asterisk (*) on those letters which she termed "special." (For her replies to letters in this series, see the appropriate date in Series VI, Outgoing Correspondence).
  - "Flying around the North Atlantic" (general), 1934 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - North to the Orient
    - General, 1935-1963 (Box 96, Folder 2-9)
    - Personal, 1935 (Box 96, Folder 10-11)
  - Listen to the Wind
    - General, 1938-1939 (Box 96, Folder 12-14)
    - General, 1939-1945 (Box 97, Folder 15-18)
  - "Adventurous Writing" (general), 1939 (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - "Prayer for Peace"
    - General, 1940 (Box 97, Folder 20-29)
    - General, 1940 (Box 98, Folder 30-36)
    - Personal, 1940 (Box 98, Folder 37-42)
    - Foreign, 1940 (Box 98, Folder 43-44)
    - Foreign, 1940 (Box 99, Folder 45)
  - "Feeding Europe"
    - General, 1940 (Box 99, Folder 46-48)
    - Requests for printed copies, 1940 (Box 99, Folder 49-52)
  - The Wave of the Future
    - General, 1940 (Box 99, Folder 53-60)
    - General (Box 100, Folder 61-71)
  - "Reaffirmation" (general), 1941 (Box 100, Folder 72-74)
  - The Steep Ascent
    - General, 1944 (Box 100, Folder 75-77)
    - General, 1944 (Box 101, Folder 78)
    - Personal, 1944 (Box 101, Folder 79-81)
  - "My Most Unforgettable Character"
    - General, 1947 (Box 101, Folder 82-87)
    - Personal, 1947 (Box 101, Folder 88)
  - "The Flame for Europe" (general), 1948 (Box 101, Folder 89-94)
  - "Airliner to Europe" (general), 1948, 1950 (Box 101, Folder 95-97)
  - Gift from the Sea
    - General, 1955 (Box 101, Folder 98-99)
    - General, 1955 (Box 102, Folder 100-109)
  - The Unicorn (general), 1956 (Box 102, Folder 110)
  - Dearly Beloved
    - General, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 111-114)
    - Personal, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 115)
  - "As I See Our First Lady" (general), 1964 (Box 102, Folder 116)
  - "Safari Back to Innocence"
    - General, 1966 (Box 102, Folder 117-118)
    - Personal, 1966 (Box 102, Folder 119)
  - "The Heron and the Astronaut" (general), 1969 (Box 103, Folder 120)
  - Earth Shine
    - General, 1969 (Box 103, Folder 121)
    - Personal, 1969 (Box 103, Folder 122)
  - Christmas in Mexico (general), 1927 (Box 103, Folder 123)
  - Bring Me a Unicorn, 1971
    - General, 1971 (Box 103, Folder 124-128)
    - Personal, 1971 (Box 103, Folder 129-132)
  - Hour of Gold, Hour of Lead
    - General, 1973 (Box 103, Folder 133-135)
    - Personal, 1973 (Box 104, Folder 136-137)
  - Bring Me a Unicorn and Hour of Gold, Hour of Lead (general), 1973 (Box 104, Folder 138)
  - Poetry, 1935-1973 (Box 104, Folder 139-140)
  - Reader comments on Anne Morrow Lindbergh's writings in general, 1939-1970 (Box 104, Folder 141)
- Outgoing correspondence, 1920-1973; Series VI; The series is arranged chronologically.
  The series contains typescripts, photocopies, and carbon copies of letters written by Lindbergh from 1920 to 1972, with the exception of letters written to her family, which are included in Series II.
  - 1920-1937 October (Box 105, Folder 1-14)
  - 1937 November-1939 (Box 106, Folder 15-27)
  - 1940 January-1941 September (Box 107, Folder 28-41)
  - 1941 October-1942 December 7 (Box 108, Folder 42-55)
  - 1942 December 8-1944 June (Box 109, Folder 56-72)
  - 1944 July-1945 July (Box 110, Folder 73-87)
  - 1945 August-1947 January (Box 111, Folder 88-101)
  - 1947 February-1948 (Box 112, Folder 102-116)
  - 1949 January-1955 May (Box 113, Folder 117-130)
  - 1955 June-1960 (Box 114, Folder 131-145)